radarurl.com 2016-03-13

# RadarURL - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy sets out how RadarURL uses and protects any information that you give RadarURL when you use this website and/or other affiliated services. RadarURL is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. RadarURL may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 18th of December, 2012.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

RadarURL does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, RadarURL.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on RadarURL.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to RadarURL.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include. 

**Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on RadarURL.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.   
RadarURL.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. Third party advertisers are not limited only to Google.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**On-Page Notification**

You are requested to add a prominent and permanent notification on all pages where you embed the RadarURL widget notifying your users that users’ anonymous information, of relevance to online behavioral advertising is being collected. We encourage you to consult with the [NAI code of conduct](http://www.networkadvertising.org/code-enforcement/code) in order to understand notification requirements. We incorporate the following paragraph as reference for you to add to your privacy policy or to be used for the said notification.  
We employ 3rd party cookies and other technologies with our widget in order to allow for non-personally identifiable information collection from users websites in addition to the information collected by our own cookies. The information is used for tracking users’ behavior anonymously (advertisement interaction, categories of interest, etc.) and technical information (geo location, language, screen resolution, etc.) in order to allow for personalized advertising: Allowing for more relevant ad serving and enhances online experience by offering more relevant content. Users may inform themselves on relevant privacy practices in our data partner’s privacy center, or opt out at any time here. We do not have access or control over these cookies that are used by third party advertisers.

**Other 3rd Party Information Collection Cookies**

We employ 3rd party cookies and other technologies with our widget in order to allow for non-personally identifiable information collection from users websites in addition to the information collected by our own cookies. The information is used for tracking users’ behavior anonymously (advertisement interaction, categories of interest, etc.) and technical information (geo location, language, screen resolution, etc.) in order to allow for personalized advertising: Allowing for more relevant ad serving and enhances online experience by offering more relevant content. Users may inform themselves on relevant privacy practices in our data partner’s [privacy center](http://www.dtscout.com/privacy_center.php), or opt out at any time [here](http://www.dtscout.com/opt-out.php). We do not have access or control over these cookies that are used by third party advertisers.

**With any further complaint, query or other interest you are welcome to contact us at support [at] radarurl [dot] com.**
